Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- Present Shock-Food Prices (Schertz, Lyle P.), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- SUNY Alumni Speech, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- "Changing Economics and Politics in Agriculture,"Agricultural Leaders' Forum (Robinson, K. L.), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Speech--The Future of Agriculture in the Northeast (WKK), 1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Rotary Speech--The New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Rotary--The Future of New York's Agriculture, Ithaca, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Dedication--H. H. Schwardt Laboratory, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Speeches--Professor Steward's Symposium, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Speech--"The Shaping of Support for the Higher Education" (Cartter, Allan M.--Chancellor, NYU), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Speech--State of the College, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Speech--"A Time for Leadership and a Time for Opportunity" (Nyquist, E. B.), 1975 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Speeches--Welcoming Remarks Pesticide Conference, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Shen, T. H. "Taiwan's Family Farm During Transitional Economic Growth", 1976 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- State Support for Agricultural Research and Extension (WKK), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Speech--State University and Its Relations with Cornell University, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- "The Future of Publicly Supported Agricultural Research" (WKK), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Speech--"The Limits of Accountability" (Bailey, Stephen K.), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- The Restless Decade (Perkins, James A.), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- "The University and Due Progress" (Perkins, J. A.), 1967 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Speech--"The University and the New Priorities" (Perkins, J. A.), 1968 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Speech--Universities and Professors in United States Society, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- "Toward a Student Syndicalist Movement" (Davidson, Carl), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Vegetable Growers, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- Speech--8th Annual Waste Management Conference, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- "Weight-Watching at the University: The Consequences of Growth", 1972 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- Welcome--New Students, 1972-1977 (Box 37, Folder 35)
- "What's Wrong With Workers' Education and What's Right" (Nash, Al), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 36)
- "Where is Biology Taking Us?" (Morison, R. S.), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 37)
- "Who Will Control Agriculture," Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 38)
- World Food Conference (WKK), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- Speeches--World Food Conference (WKK), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- Comments From Agricultural Faculty on College Study-- "The New York State College of Agriculture and the Next Quarter Century", 1967 (Box 37, Folder 41)
- New York State College of Agriculture (WKK), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 42)
- Cohn Farm, 1976-1977 (Box 37, Folder 43)
- Cohn Farm, 1975-1976 (Box 37, Folder 44)
- Cohn Farm, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Cohn Farm, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Cohn Farm--Wayne County Housing Opportunities, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 47)
- Cohn Farm Agreement, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- Cohn Farm, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- Cohn Farm Procedures to Operate, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 50)
- Cohn Farm, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 51-52)
- Cohn Farm, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 53-55)
- Cohn Farm, 1962-1970 (Box 37, Folder 56-57)
- Cohn Farm (Formerly Horn Farm)--Sodus, New York, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 58)
- Cohn Farm Early Reports (Given to Dean by Pomology Department 1971), 1939-1961 (Box 37, Folder 59-60)
- Cohn Farm--Background of Gift, 1960-1969 (Box 37, Folder 61)
- Rochester Gas and Electric, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 62)
- Isles of Shoals, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 63)
- Isles of Shoals, 1971-1972 (Box 37, Folder 64-65)
- Isles of Shoals, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 66-67)
- Isles of Shoals, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 68-69)
- Isles of Shoals Trip, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 70)
- Isles of Shoals, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Isles of Shoals, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
- Salaries, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
- Space, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Vegetable Crops, 1966-1970 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Hartman, John D.--Dismissal Proceedings, 1967-1973 (Box 38, Folder 8-12)
- Hartman, John--Dismissal Hearing, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 13-18)
- Hartman, John--Documents Submitted to Faculty Hearing Board by John Hartman, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 19-24)
- Pierce, Ellis A., 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Patton, R. L.--Grievance Procedure, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 26-29)
- Building Programs, 1965-1971 (Box 38, Folder 30-31)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding Conservation Building NIH, 1964-1970 (Box 38, Folder 32-33)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding Conservation Building NIH, 1962-1964 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding-Conservation Building NSF, 1964-1969 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding-Conservation Building NSF, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
- Award Statement NIH, 1962-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5-6)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding-Conservation Building, 1966-1970 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Photographs--Agronomy Building, 1965-1967 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Plant Science Renovation, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding-Conservation Building NSF, 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Agronomy-Plant Breeding-Conservation Building NIH, 1965-1967 (Box 39, Folder 11-12)
- Agronomy Building, 1965-1967 (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
- Agronomy Building (GU-108), 1963-1967 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Cell Physiology, Growth, and Development, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Biological Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
- Current and Proposed Long-Term Support for Division of Biological Sciences at Cornell University, 1966-1968 (Box 39, Folder 19-20)
- Research and Educational Program of New York State College of Agriculture, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Biology and Society, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Biological Sciences--Reports, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 23-24)
- Biological Sciences, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 25-27)
- Biological Sciences--Support for, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 28-29)
- Biological Sciences, 1968-1970 (Box 39, Folder 30-31)
- Biology Report, 1965-1968 (Box 39, Folder 32-33)
- Current and Proposed Long-Term Support for the Division of Biological Sciences at Cornell University, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- SUNY--Construction Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- SUNY--Director of Employee Relations (Wollett), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- SUNY--Executive Vice Chancellor (Kelly, James), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- SUNY--Faculty Senate, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- SUNY--Master Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Director of Personnel Research (Egerton, Will), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- SUNY--Provost (Baritz, Loren), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- SUNY--Research and Graduate Education, Office of Academic Policy (WKK-Consultant), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Academic Policy (Baritz, Loren), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- SUNY--Academic Programs (Van Arnam, Kathryn), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Campus Development (Lanford, Oscar), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations (Komisar, Jerome), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance and Business (Spindler, Harry), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for University Affairs (Thorne, Clifton), 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- SUNY--Washington Office, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- SUNY--Community Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- SUNY--Stony Brook, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- SUNY--Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Department Heads' Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Statutory Deans' Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- SUNY--Office of Academic Policy, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- SUNY--Assistant Chancellor for Special Projects (Neff, Charles B.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- SUNY--Associate Chancellor for Public Services (Ingler, Charles), 1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- SUNY--Budget Request, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- SUNY--Chancellor (Boyer, Ernest L.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- SUNY--Chancellor's Award for Excellence in Teaching, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Vice President for Research (Cooke, W.D.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Vice Provost (Barlow, Mark), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Vice Provost (McKeegan, Paul), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Committee of Chairmen, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Deans and Directors Agendas, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Deans and Directors Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Dean's Council, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 18-19)
- Board of Trustees, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 20-21)
- Dean of the Faculty (Saunders, W. B.), 1976 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Legislative and Governmental Relations Assistant (Andersen, Fred Lee), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- President (Corson, D. R.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- President-Elect (Rhodes, Frank H. T.), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Presidential Search, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Provost (Knapp, D. C.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 27-28)
- Senior Vice President (Herbster, William G.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Treasurer (Peterson, A. H.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Vice President for Campus Affairs (Gurowitz, William D.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Vice President and Chief Investment Officer (Horn, Robert), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Vice President for Land-Grant Affairs (Cook, Constance E.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 33-34)
- Vice President for Public Affairs (Ramin, R. M.), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Agricultural Economics, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 36-37)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Agronomy, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Steponkus, Peter L., 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Animal Science, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 41-42)
- Animal Science Teaching and Research Center (ASTARC)--Outlook Conference, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Communication Arts, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Education, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 46-47)
- Entomology, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Cooperative Extension, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- County Agents, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Finance and Business Office, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Floriculture, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Food Science, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Geneva, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 54-55)
- Institute of Food Science Advisory Council, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Poultry, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Microbiology, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Landscape Architecture, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 59)
- International Agricultural Development (IAD), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Natural Resources, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 61)
- Plant Breeding, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 62)
- Biometry, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Plant Pathology, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Pomology, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 65)
- Institute of Food Science, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Research, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Research Examples, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Resident Instruction, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
- Minority Program for College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Placement--Agriculture and Life Sciences (Gerling, Michael J.), 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Director of Resident Instruction Search Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Rural Sociology, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Vegetable Crops, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Lab, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Correspondence--A, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Accessory Instruction, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Administrative Assignments in the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Advisers (WKK), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Affirmative Action, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- AgPAC, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Council of Agricultural Advisors to DEC, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forums, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Resource Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 23-24)
- United States Secretary of Agriculture, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Agway, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Alumni Association, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Alumni Office, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- American Agriculturist, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- ARPAC, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 30-31)
- ARS Meeting on Animal Agriculture in the Northeast--Harrisburg, PA, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Association of Teachers of Agriculture of New York, Inc. (ATANY), 1976 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Austin Farm, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Correspondence--B, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Bank--Farm Credit of Springfield, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Cornell Black Agriculturalists, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Division of Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 39)
- School of Business and Public Administration, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Correspondence--C, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Chairs, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Commissioner of Commerce, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 43)
- The Federation of Cornell Clubs, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 45)
- Cornell Plantations, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 46)
- COSEP, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 47)
- Correspondence--D, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 48)
- Dairylea, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 49)
- Dairy Herd Improvement, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 50)
- Dean's College Funds--Allocations, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 51)
- Dean's List, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 52)
- Dean's Reception, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 53)
- University Development, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 54)
- Correspondence--E, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 55)
- New York State Department of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 56)
- Empire Farm Days, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 57)
- Empire State Potato Club, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 58)
- Endowed College Capital Needs Through 1981, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 59)
- College of Engineering, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 60)
- Grading Trends in the College of Engineering, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 61)
- New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 62)
- Environmental Protection Agency, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 63)
- College of Environmental Sciences and Forestry, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 64)
- Environmental Science and Forestry and Agriculture and Life Sciences Collaboration, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 65)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 66)
- Correspondence--F, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 67)
- United States Food and Drug Administration, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 68)
- Food and Life Science Quarterly, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 69)
- Freezes, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 70)
- Future Farmers of America, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 71)
- Correspondence--G, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 72)
- Garden Living Industries of the Eastern United States, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 73)
- Graduate School, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 74)
- Correspondence--H, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 75)
- Highlights--1975 Edition, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 76)
- Horticultural Society, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 77)
- Hudson Basin Project, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 78)
- Hudson Valley Lab, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 79)
- College of Human Ecology, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 80)
- Correspondence--I, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 81)
- Indirect Costs, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 82)
- School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 83)
- International Development and Food Assistance Act of 1975-19-Title XII, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 84)
- Center of International Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 85)
- Isles of Shoals, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 86-87)
- Correspondence--J, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 88)
- Correspondence--K, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 89)
- King, Joe, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 90)
- Correspondence--L, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 91)
- Law School, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 92)
- Libraries, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 93)
- Lily Endowment, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 94)
- Legislative Bills and Acts, 1976-1975 (Box 41, Folder 95)
- Legislative Bills and Acts, 1969-1976 (Box 41, Folder 96-97)
- Senators, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 98)
- Assembly Intern Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 99)
- Members of Assembly, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Members of Congress, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
- Governor's Office, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Correspondence--M, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Master Plan, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Milk Prices, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Milk Study, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Miner Institute, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Correspondence--Mc, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Myers, William I., 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 11-13)
- Correspondence--N, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- National Science Board, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Native Americans, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- New Faculty Reception, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- New York Farm Electrification Council, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- New York Soil Conservation Districts Association, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- New York State Grange, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- New York Farmers, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Nutritional Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 26-27)
- Correspondence--O, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Ornithology Lab, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Correspondence--P, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Pest Control Strategies Symposium, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Pesticide Application Certification, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 34-35)
- Pesticides, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 36)
- President of the United States--Office of Science and Technology Policy, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Special Professorships, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Public Information, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Correspondence--R, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Reception--Graduation Day, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Regents of the University of the State of New York, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Rental Housing, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 43)
- The Research Foundation, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Responsibility Center Analysis, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Retiring Faculty, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- Ritchie, Maureen, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Northeast Regional Center Rural Development, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Rural Development--Clinton County, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Correspondence--S, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Sabbatical Leaves, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Salaries, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 52)
- Sea Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 53-54)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 55)
- Social Analysis Science System (SASS), 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 56)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 57)
- Soil Resource Inventory Workshop, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 58)
- St. Lawrence, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 59)
- Stationery, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Steward, F. C., 1976 (Box 42, Folder 61)
- Dean of Students, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 62)
- Student Support Services Study, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 63)
- Community Symposium, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--T, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 65)
- Tissue Culture Facility, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 66)
- Title V, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 67-68)
- Title XII, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 69-70)
- Toward the Year 1985-19-Updating, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 71)
- Tuition, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 72)
- Correspondence--U, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 73)
- University Council, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 74)
- Cornell University Press, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 75)
- University Senate, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 76)
- USDA, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 77)
- United States Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Lab, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 78)
- Correspondence--V, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 79)
- Veterinary College, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 80)
- Correspondence--W, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 81)
- World Food Conference, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 82)
- Committee on Academic Freedom and Responsibility, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 83)
- Committee on Academic Programs and Policies, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 84)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Advisory Fund Council, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 85)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund Advisory Council, 1975-1976 (Box 42, Folder 86)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Appointment Procedures, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 87-88)
- Aquaculture Steering Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 42, Folder 89)
- University Committee on Biohazards, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 90)
- University Calendar Commission--Special Commission to Consider, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
- College Admissions Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- College Seed Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Communication Arts--Education Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Communication Support Services Search Committee (Call, D. L.--Chrm.), 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- University Computing Board, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
- Cornell Plantations Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Committee on Course Announcements, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Division Committee on Aid Liaison and Budget (Tefertiller--Chrm.), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Committee to Study Economic and Professional Status, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Education Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Educational Policy Committee (Agriculture and Life Sciences), 1972-1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Energy (College) Task Force, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Faculty Council of Representatives (Agriculture and Life Sciences), 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Inauguration Committee for President Rhodes, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Intercollege Activity Committees, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Committee on Joint Appointments, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Natural Resources Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- New York Farm Bureau 1975 Resolutions Committee, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- New York State Rural Development Council, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Physiology Committee (VanTienhoven--Chrm.), 1975 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Plant Science Curriculum Committee, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- President's Committee on Science and Technology, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Committee on Professional and Economic Status of the Faculty (Flash--Chrm.), 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Commission on Purposes and Priorities (SUNY), 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Committee on Review of Deans and Directors, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- President's Commission on Self-Governance, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Snyder and Morris Scholarship Award Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- New York State Soil and Water Conservation, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- SUNY--Cornell Task Force, 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 32-33)
- SUNY--Provost for Research Search Committee, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Task Force--"Centers and Interdisciplinary Programs", 1975 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Tenure Committee (VanDemark--Chrm., Everett, Call), 1974 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Undergraduate Business Education at Cornell (Davidson, Justin), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Biological Sciences Director Search Committee, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Tyler Ecology Award Committee, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 39)
- University Lecture Committee, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- Circular Letters (WKK), 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 41)
- Associate Dean, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 42)